mortgagecove.com 2013-11-26

# None

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") discloses the privacy practices for the website that linked you here. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy here. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of current practices, as they may change in the future. 

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. 

We do not collect personal information about you. We only obtain information about your desired loan type, credit rating, and zip code. We send this information to the mortgage companies that we work with to decide which company links to display to you. We do not store this information. 

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to the site, such as browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. 

This website is directed at adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

This privacy policy is effective as of November 30, 2012.
